Smartphones have always posed challenges for parents of teens.
智能手机一直给青少年的父母带来挑战。
From social media apps to excessive screen time, the digital world is as threatening as the physical.
从社交媒体应用到过长的屏幕使用时间，数字世界和现实世界一样充满威胁。
A new study shows that about half of parents of teens are worried about their teens being exposed to explicit content online.
一项新研究显示，在青少年的父母中，约有一半担心孩子在网上接触到露骨内容。
This is a valid concern, of course.
当然，这是一种合理的担忧。
But there are ways to alleviate the spread of explicit content, from changing the settings in their kids’ phones to monitoring such content with apps like Bark.
但有一些办法可以减少露骨内容的传播，从更改孩子手机上的设置，到用Bark之类的应用监控这类内容，不一而足。
Just as alarming, if not more so, is that the amount of time teens spend on social media can lead to anxiety and depression.
同样令人忧虑、甚至有过之而无不及的是，青少年花在社交媒体上的时长可能导致焦虑和抑郁。
Excessive screen time has detrimental effects, for a lot of obvious reasons.
过长的屏幕使用时间会造成有害影响，原因有很多，而且显而易见。
Constant media consumption inhibits healthy activities associated with childhood, like spending time outside, exercising, talking to friends and family.
不停地消费媒体内容会妨碍与童年相关的健康活动，比如待在户外、锻炼身体、和朋友家人聊天。
If it interferes with sleep, that’s even worse.
如果干扰到睡眠，那就更糟了。
Ample research shows too much smartphone use produces significant anxiety, depression, and feelings of isolation in teens.
大量研究表明，过度使用智能手机会让青少年产生严重的焦虑、抑郁和孤立感。
Teens log on to social media or spend time online trying to make connections, but end up feeling more alone and sadder than ever.
青少年登录社交媒体或花时间上网，想与人建立联系，最后却感到比以往任何时候都更孤单、更难过。
Faceless communication not only produces feelings of isolation and loneliness but increases instances of online bullying and susceptibility to criminal conduct.
不见面的交流不仅会让人产生孤立感和孤独感，还会增加网络欺凌事件，并使人更容易受到犯罪行为的影响。
Though I’ve banned most social media, I’ve still battled smartphone time with my own kids.
虽然我已经禁止自己的孩子使用大部分社交媒体，但还是一直在为智能手机使用时间和他们较劲。
A lot of the time I wish I could throw my kids’ smartphones into the nearest lake.
很多时候，我真希望能把孩子们的智能手机扔进最近的湖里。
The convenience of communication—when they need a ride home from school after practice, for instance—often feels like it isn’t worth the battle to keep their screen time low and productive, and continue to encourage “real-life” activities outside and with friends and family.
通讯上的便利——比如孩子训练结束后需要有人从学校接他们回家的时候——常常让人觉得抵不上这番较劲：既要让孩子的屏幕使用时间少而有益，又要继续鼓励他们在户外、和朋友家人一起参加“现实生活”中的活动。
I understand the addiction and often tell them I’m not sure how I would have handled having a smartphone as a teen.
我理解这种瘾，还常常跟他们说，要是我十几岁时有智能手机，我不确定自己会怎么应对。
As an adult, I, too, struggle with overuse.
作为成年人，我自己也苦于过度使用手机。
In a recent TV interview to promote a new film about a mother and daughter navigating social media use, actress Kate Winslet expressed her view on teens and social media—and her concern mirrors the trends.
女演员凯特·温斯莱特最近为宣传一部新电影接受了电视采访，影片讲述一对母女如何应对社交媒体使用问题；她在采访中表达了自己对青少年与社交媒体的看法，而她的担忧反映了上述趋势。
“I do definitely feel that the world of social media is frightening to parents because we don’t really know what’s there,” she said.
“我确确实实地感到，社交媒体的世界令父母害怕，因为我们并不真正知道那里面有什么。”她说。
“We don’t know how our children are using it.
“我们不知道孩子们是怎么使用它的。
We don’t know the effects that it’s really having on them.”
我们不知道它究竟在对孩子们产生什么影响。”
I don’t think the US government should regulate social media and teen smartphone use, but it is a vital topic for parents to understand and take seriously.
我不认为美国政府应该监管社交媒体和青少年使用智能手机的行为，但这是一个至关重要的话题，父母需要了解并认真对待。
Unfortunately, now, parents don’t just have to worry about real-world dangers, but also about all the ones sneaking online and the effects they have on teenagers and their mental health.
遗憾的是，如今父母不仅要担心现实世界中的危险，还要担心在网上悄然出没的所有危险，以及这些危险对青少年及其心理健康造成的影响。